## Charlotte Nightingale

# Full stack software developer and Certified Scrum Master

I am looking to join a software team as a full stack or backend developer. I have many years experience of working collaboratively and I have studied the Full Stack Track at Mayden Academy.

#### **PROJECTS:**

Grub recipe app: <a href="http://bit.ly/35jc7yq">http://bit.ly/35jc7yq</a>

Working as an agile team we built an OOP PHP recipe app to display and save recipes based on an ingredients list. We used the Hydrator entity pattern to create objects directly from a MySQL database. We consumed the Recipe Puppy API as a data source, while validating and sanitising all user input.

#### Gecko card matching app: <a href="http://bit.ly/37lqCDk">http://bit.ly/37lqCDk</a>

Working as an agile team we built a Javascript matching game where the player matches duplicate pictures of geckos. We used Github as a team and it reinforced the importance of granularising the backlog tasks so that work was available to all team members.

### Aptitude test: <a href="http://bit.ly/32UaHbW">http://bit.ly/32UaHbW</a>

We collaborated on a legacy project using JavaScript, incorporating Gulp and SCSS, extending an online aptitude test. We built modals to incorporate user functionality for editing and deleting questions, and we gained useful experience in story estimation and keeping story branches uncontaminated.

#### **JOB HISTORY:**

7/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/ 1/	I A a Chart Variation	roloc toaching	AVamining	I and tutoring	childran in Scianca and
2000-2019:	TEACHEL VALIOUS	TOTES TEACTION			i children in Science and

Psychology at secondary schools in London and Bath.

1997-2000: Administrative roles and bar work during my undergraduate studies in London.

1994-1997: Administrative roles in insurance, IT and media organisations in London.

1992-1993: Bar work during undergraduate studies at Manchester University (uncompleted).

#### **EDUCATION**

2019: Full Stack Track at Mayden Academy, Bath (software developer training course).

2014 - 2016: MSc Biosciences (Merit) University of Bath (using a python pipeline in my project).

1997 - 2000: BSc Biological Sciences (First) King's College London.